{
    "subject": "resource/WUSA_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "WUSA is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8592895269393921,
            "question": "How is WUSA different from other types of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8212751746177673,
            "question": "Is WUSA a popular form of entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6855342388153076,
            "question": "What kind of media is WUSA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740094780921936,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a WUSA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5193657875061035,
            "question": "Give an example of a WUSA."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5099490284919739,
            "question": "Is WUSA a type of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4810713231563568,
            "question": "Can you describe the typical content of a WUSA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45132818818092346,
            "question": "What are some popular genres within WUSA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06774528324604034,
            "question": "Are there any famous examples of WSUs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05751528590917587,
            "question": "Where can you typically find WSUs to watch?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WUSA is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7478_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous examples of WSUs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7478_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular genres within WUSA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7478_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the typical content of a WUSA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7478_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7478_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain information about the movie WUSA, including its genre. In one of the documents, it is mentioned that \"Genre - Romance\" and also another document mentions \"WUSA is a prime, if somewhat staid, example of Liberal Nightmare Cinema, I\u2019m talking about that curiously indestructible subgenre of films...\". This implies that WUSA is indeed a type of film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the context that discusses \"WUSA\" as a film, mentioning it has actors, a director, and scenes, which aligns with the description of a cinematic work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}